I must be dreaming tonight
We erase it from our memories
You can't escape
I only know this secret with you
How can I protect you forever?
Close your eyes
I'll be anything for you
I can't live this life
Without you by my side...
「I'll believe..」
Right now the real world is black out, it's black out
世界全体が一斉 Shout down
鳴り響きやまないアラートの業火 その中
Look at the color of fire 照らしたもの一切を
奪ってしまうほどに deepest black
I can't live life
Without you by my side..
「I'll believe..」 孤独も因縁さえ
Yeah, yeah
灼熱の記録の欠片
現在を映す brightness
Can see your light
あなたを照らした光彩が
わたしの記憶にも在るなら
I'm sure that we can go
全てを証明していこう
存在していく為の理由を
Inside of Kaos I say
Where can I get the real love and fate, right now?
How can I make you know
my heart is with you hey?...
届かない想いでも構わない
たとえこの身滅び 消え去っても行くゼ.
人間は誰も忘れていく
痛めた傷跡も
時間の流れ見送る度に
薄れる感情
だけどこれ以上見過ごしたくなくて
Back and forth 心中叫んでやまない
Time over
消えていく残像それは あなたそのものだから
So now that you & I
I can't live life
Without you by my side...
「I'll believe..」孤独も因縁さえ
Yeah, yeah
灼熱の記録の欠片
現在を映す brightness
Can see your light
あなたを照らした光彩が
わたしの記憶にも在るなら
I'm sure that we can go
全てを証明していこう
存在していく為の理由を
Hey hey 目の前のフィード 抗えない運命ならば
この身を挺して この手で戦いたいから
I believe that you will see what
I'm doing is never wrong for us
そうさ もう何も恐れはしない 「I'll believe」
「覚えている」その事実で
生きる術を知る
悠久の闇切り裂く程に
報われぬ想い
だから一つだけ覚えててほしくて
Back and forth 心中叫んでやまない
Time ever
涙の瘡蓋でさえ 愛すべき残像だと
So now that you & I
I can't live life
Without you by my side...
「I'll believe..」心に刻んだ意志
Yeah, yeah
闘いの業火の中で
何度も見つけ出して
Refrain again
世界が空虚に塗れても
あなたの記憶に宿ってる
Telling me what I got now
確かな炎に気付いて
存在する理由が「此処」に在ると
Bre-bre-bre-break down
Now it's a show time, The night is so deep
轟音の最中の その静寂
Get ready to the next stage また時計が今日を全部
ゼロにしていくけれど 想いはずっと胸
募ってくばかりの 遠ざかってくあなたの 薫りを抱きしめて
And just nobody この昴まり 魂の塊
聴こえないとしても構わない あなただけに
ずっとその胸に その手にその夢に
全部届いてると信じれるこの愛
だから一つだけ覚えててほしくて
Back and forth 心中叫んでやまない
Time forever
二度と独りにしないと 愛するあなたのこと
So now that you & I
I can't live life
Without you by my side...
「I'll believe..」孤独も因縁さえ
Yeah, Yeah
灼熱の記録の欠片
未来を映す brightness
Can see your light
あなたを照らした光彩が
わたしの記憶にも在るから
I'm sure that we can go
全てを証明していこう
存在していく為の理由を
全身全霊でいま刻む自分の今日
共存していく未来を
「I'll believe..」
Yeah 「I'll believe..」